Ow! Ow!
Cramp! Help!
- June.
- She's faking it.
Just like everything
about her is fake.
Help!
- I'm coming!
- [WATER SPLASHES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Ow!
- [PING] I got you.
- [JUNE] Ow!
- [PING] Wait.
[PING] Just relax, okay?
[JUNE] That hurt! Ouch!
[PING] Just relax.
[PING HUFFS]
- [PING] Where does it hurt?
- [JUNE] This foot.
[PING] Wait.
- Ow! Ow!
- [PING] Relax.
[JUNE] Oh, my god.
I would've shaved my legs if I
had known this would happen.
He might think my skin
is made of sandpaper.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC BECOMES ROMANTIC]
[GIGGLING]
- Ow!
- Oh!
Sor-- Sorry, sorry, sorry!
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
I didn't mean to.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Why'd you hit me there?
- Sorry.
- Oh my god, sir!
Do you need ice?
Just get my stuff.
Just get my stuff, hurry.
I'll get it.
[PING GROANS]
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Why do you have
my birth certificate?
And also Ima's, my uncle's,
and my cousins'?
Huh?
Are you having me
investigated?
This isn't part of our
agreement.
- Come here.
- Hey! What are you doing?!
I might fall!
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]